you know what else is not stealing
putting an extra bike lock on a
stranger's bike
it's insane that bike locks are legal
that they're just available to the
public you have any idea the amount of
power that you wield
with your imagination and a bike lock
there's so many things like you could
just walk past the baskin robbins and be
like you're closed
it is so arbitrary what we need
permission to buy and what we don't you
have to show photo id
in a hobby shop to buy paint yet all of
us here are just one amazon click away
from buying orange cones and making
traffic go wherever we want
i don't like buying milk right they
don't sell any other product that way
you grab a bag of marshmallows off the
shelf all the other marshmallows don't
come at you
milk the heaviest item in the store they
sell on a ramp that's aimed at your face
i mean pull one gallon off seven others
slam forward
it's two percent you wanted non-fat but
now you can't put it back
i discovered though you push those other
milks hard enough they disappear
in the healthy grocery stores i i never
buy anything from that aisle of barrels
i just don't like how accessible it is
to like bare hands
or the air
here's what i do though i go up to the
most expensive granola and i scoop it
into the cheapest one
i'm the robin hood of whole foods
my wife and i were very different we
come from different backgrounds like i
came from a normal family you know
she she just came from like a hippie
dippy family you know her dad's an
actual hippie her mom's a holistic nurse
and i just if first of all if you don't
know what holistic medicine is
it's basically like
remember when you were little
and you play house you know you let you
pretend you had to go to the doctor but
you're a kid so you don't have medical
equipment so you just kind of use sticks
and rocks and stuff
that's holistic medicine
here's here's a better example when i
was single before i met my wife i used
to use irish spring okay it's good soap
i like it
that was my soap
and then i met my wife we got married we
move in together she sees my soap in the
shower one day
and she freaks out she's like whoa whoa
whoa whoa what what is this come here
what is this
are you kidding me
that
that has aluminum in it that's terrible
that has aluminum in it i'm like i'm
like
uh
i i didn't see any
she's like you cannot use that you can't
use that here you got to use this weird
misshapen oatmeal rock i bought from a
homeless person at the farmer's market
this is what your body needs
it's the good stuff
all right whatever hey i'm a married guy
i don't want to make waves i know how it
goes right so i'm using her
soap okay
first of all it hurts because there's
pebbles in it
i don't know who's running quality
control at the hippy dippy soap factory
but i think they're asleep with the
wheels there's a lot of junk going down
that line no one's pecking out
i'm using her soap one day i'm washing
myself i cut my leg
i literally cut my leg i looked down
there's a stick
in the soap you ever cut yourself
soaping anyone
it's very frustrating
i never found a stick in my irish spring
okay
that's kind of a big selling point when
i when i buy soap no sticks
look at that one
i just don't get this hippy-dippy
movement we're all moving towards or you
know oh you shouldn't you don't you
shouldn't wash yourself with anything
and unless you found it on the ground in
the woods
that's how you know it's good soap
i used to go to target and i'd buy a
year supply of irish spring and it would
cost me i think what i don't know eleven
dollars
comes in a box
made in a factory it says soap on the
side somewhere
so you know what you're buying
meanwhile my wife's buying soap from
gypsies
made out of oatmeal and sticks
right
the packaging is rope
that's good quality control right there
the label is just a ripped off piece of
scratch paper someone hand wrote
nature's chunk of crap
eighteen dollars
okay
so anyways the girl the girl i'm with um
she uh her
her family likes to go to jersey shore
video i told you i live in boston so she
like her family likes to go to jersey
shore it's a big vacation destination we
all go to lbi long beach island is crazy
beach time it's it's everybody's on the
beach so i thought it was going to be
nuts i thought it was gonna be like it's
gonna be a party no okay here's what
happens uh they we we go rent this house
for a week and whole family and they
wake up at like six in the morning right
and they drag out all the stuff out of
the house and they bring it to the beach
couches chairs cans of food sandwiches
books her mom's like you got a book
you're gonna need a book honey you got a
book you're gonna need a book for you
got a book you're gonna really need a
book you gotta i was like why do i need
a book she said because we're gonna be
here all day
i had no idea they were all just gonna
sit on the beach and cook in the sun
and then they all just flipped like
little rotisserie chickens and they just
keep going
and at one point our mom looked at me
and she was like are you having a good
time honey i was like yeah i'm having a
good time because i'm respectful but i
wasn't having a good time
i wanted to be like what do you want me
to do lay on my back and tan the bottoms
of my hands and my feet i'm tan already
how long are we gonna stay here
[Music]
her dad by the third day her dad's
always peeling from his forehead he's
peeling from his nose he's like i don't
know how i got burned this year i'm like
really you don't know how you got burned
this year what happened did the sun
trick you this year is that what
happened
did it somehow hide behind the moon and
it just popped out like burn baby bird
jump back behind the moon and hit
what do you mean
[Music]
her brother always takes his little
pasty arm and he puts it back next to my
arm right like the second day he's like
look at me bro i'm almost as dark as you
i'm just docking here
[Music]
i really use that you know how scared
you would be
if you woke up one morning
and just the right side of your face
was my complexion as a white you'd be
like
turn it into a panda
you'd be so scared
[Music]
one of the days i'm sitting there with
everybody i said give me the 50. putting
on the sunblock i said give me the 50.
my girl and putting on the 50 whatever
he starts laughing the brother slapped
he's like why are you putting my
sunscreen i'm like why are you laughing
he goes because you're putting our sun
block i was like yeah why are you
laughing he goes because you don't need
it i was like yes i do need it
he was like why i said because i'm made
out of meat that's why what do you mean
why
this is skin what are you thinking what
do you mean why
he's like relax i just didn't think you
needed it i thought i grew up thinking
black people didn't need sunscreen i was
like that's the thing you grew up
learning he was like yeah that's what i
thought i didn't know just
assimilated into my brain somehow i'm
not racist clearly i'm hanging out with
you right now so
[Music]
he's like i didn't know
you know what's messed up as i look at
your faces i feel like you're looking at
me like i didn't think you needed it
either
that's a problem
black people need sunscreen what is
wrong with you
what do you think happened to morgan
freeman's face
all those chocolate chips on his face
that's from the sun
that's not genetic it was in the cell
with no sunscreen
i should have put a little sunscreen on
my face
another time
so my wife and i uh we talk
probably
a lot about
mostly kids stuff
i actually have kids in the house and
kids they take up
they take up a lot
clap if you have children i'm telling
you
kids take up
a lot
okay
we have
two boys okay we have a ten-year-old and
a three-year-old and i hate to have to
say it but technically to the 10 year
old i'm his stepdad and i hate to have
to make a distinction because that's not
how we live at my house
but i've been there since he was four a
buddy of mine he goes yeah well you know
do you treat him like he's really your
kid
i go yeah i've been there since he was
four you know i'm the one who taught
this kid out of peace standing up
all right i taught him my morals i
taught him when your mom serves you
breakfast first thing you do is say
thank you right those are my morals and
i pay his rent
that's how if i pay your rent you're my
son
that's the rules
[Music]
it works he's my buddy we play xbox
together
my friend's like yeah yeah i get it you
know playing xbox i'm just saying you
know
what if there's a fire
then how important is he
and i was like dude
i still gotta face my wife after the
fire
i can't walk up to her holding the xbox
like whoa that was close
[Applause]
we made it
what
no he was right behind me
that's terrible
because he had the other controller
no
i love this dude he's my buddy he's my
little buddy he's my sidekick right
and i'll tell you this okay so this two
boys
have different dads my wife
is caucasian
that means white
the school system here
her first husband
also black
i tell you that so now you know exactly
what the kids look like because we only
make one basic floor model
you feel bad but you know exactly what
they look like
coco skin curly hair
so when the 10 year old he was little i
would take him with me to the store all
the time this used to happen all the
time usually girls department stores go
oh my goodness he looks just like you
i totally see it father and son he looks
just like you
he doesn't look like me
at all they're not going by facial
features they're going by a color chart
he's in between this color and this
color
that's not how it works
he looks exactly like his dad like so
much so sometimes when i talk to him i
just punch him in the mouth
told you not to just oh it's you buddy
it's you buddy it's
buddy i told you not to make that face
buddy don't make
your mom's coming get up get up get up
get up get up get out get up get up get
out he was on the floor when i got here
he's playing lay down
now listen i'm telling you this because
this is 100 true story i'm not making
this up okay
this is this kid's background
he's four years old
it happened three times in one day
people oh you look just like each other
he's starting to get it four years old
we're leaving toys r us happened three
times in one setting he's leaving he
looks at me because hey uh um hey warren
um how come
how come people keep thinking you're my
dad
and i go
i don't know buddy probably probably
because we're both black
and he says
i'm not black
okay
what uh
what are you buddy
and he goes i'm white
i go you are white
but you are also
black
straight face he goes what am i black
and i said
every other weekend
and alternating holidays
it's gonna be a dark easter buddy
but it's going to be a white christmas
[Applause]
best of both worlds buddy
actually it's uh it's coming up on my uh
on my anniversary october will be my
anniversary um october i was uh
oh man seven six six years ago
six years ago in october this year
october would be six years i was
diagnosed with colon cancer
i had the cancer removed uh six year
will be my six year anniversary in
october being done with it
and um thank you
i had i had to lose the weight uh
six years ago i was about 300 343 pounds
holy crap
i was 343 pounds now i'm at 270 274 273
pounds
trying to get down
trying to get it out and i'm telling you
something fellas we need to be more
aware we do we need to be more aware of
of of our i know a lot of guys think
they superman that's what i like to do
when i do my shows i like to talk to the
fellas and be like you know what we need
to get our awareness up
because i'll give you all a real number
7 out of 10 guys
70 percent of guys
will die from either prostate colon or
testicular cancer
that's real 70 of us because we don't
have no awareness we don't say enough we
keep it in we're superman we're not to
say nothing i know most men will stand
in a crooked position because something
hurts just tennis
you know what i'm talking about you go
to work you see field phil's standing
like this
you walk past me like phil what's wrong
no need to go away leave me alone
and fellas do we help phil no we don't
help phil we make fun of phil the whole
night
every time we see phil hey phil
we need to stop phil needs to see a
doctor fellas
we need to be aware we need to be we
need to get our awareness up like the
ladies ladies your awareness is
fantastic fantastic if there's something
wrong in the female world you will let
everybody know
you will stop people do you know what
today is
but that's good that's fantastic you
would never let your best friend stand
there crooked
your best friend's cricket you'd be like
girl what's wrong with you
what's this
straighten yourself up fix yourself
that's what we need to do fellas we need
to be like that
don't go through what i went through
don't wait till the last minute before
you got to go see your daughter if it's
time to go see your doctor go see your
doctor don't go through it or what
because they did a lot of stuff back
here
they did but i'm glad they got it out
i'm glad it was done after all my
surgeries after everything was done
after all of that my recovery i have a
new respect for you ladies now
i do
because i had to be y'all for a little
bit
for real when i was going through my
recovery from from the surgeries i was
still a little
i was still bleeding in the back side so
i had to wear
maxi pads
for about two weeks
it's not funny
i didn't even know they had a sticky
side
didn't
i didn't know how they worked
mine just moved around every time i
walked
i walked around like no this is not
right this is not right
this is why they always mad no i get it
now
i had to call my sister but i was like
how do you keep these things still
she was like did you peel it i'm like
did i peel what
she was like that little piece of paper
what did you think that was i thought it
was an air freshener i don't know how
these work
she was like no you idiot you peel it
stick it then you're good so i did
and it was fantastic
after that i was like okay there it is
there it is
i was giving random ladies high fives
stay free